Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ooh.
Whoa.
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Yay!
Teenager.
Teenagers.
Wow.
Aah!
Oh no!
I can't do it, I'm going to throw up.
I'm so nervous.
I get all teary-eyed in front of the camera.
I've been waiting for Kanako-chan and wanted to give her a birthday present.
Today was the only day I could give it to her in person.
I've been waiting for this opportunity for a long time.
Here it comes... here it comes...
What should I do? I'm so embarrassed!
Wait a minute, I really can't do it.
I'm so nervous.
What should I do?
I'm so embarrassed!
Oh no!
Thank you for watching!
Pretty for you
On the green line
Hell me now
If it's a word, I don't need it anymoreIf it's a word, I don't need it anymore
It's up now It's up out
Yoemi
It's so cute
I'm sorry
You sure? Is it okay? Yeah? Is it okay?
I don't know what you like.
Really? Really?
It's cute
Let's open it
What? It's cute? Is it cute? Just a little bit? Is it okay?
It's okay.
What? Is it cute? Look at it? It's cute. Look at it
It's the season from here
I saw it on Instagram
It's so cute
It's good
It's definitely good
I'm so happy
I love it
Thank you.
Okay. One, two.
One, two, three.
Last one.
Thank you.
I'm so nervous
I'm so nervous.
Why?
Please do a medley after this Please do a medley after this
Please do a medley after this
It was Kanako
It was Aira
Why are you crying? Why are you crying?
Please stop
I can't get through to Kanako every year
Why are you crying? Why are you crying?
I regret it
No, seriously, I hate it
Stop it
Hey.
Ah!
Ta-da! We've got another Sahol from Flound Oop!
CAPTURED! He's been captured!
Cute. What do I get?
Oh, uh, not that kind of thing.
I'm not doing it. Let's go home.
I won't let you go.
Oh, no, no, no.
I didn't tell them what I was going to do.
I didn't tell them what the purpose of this was, but I just wanted to ask them a few questions.
I think I'd like to ask a few questions with my guessers.
I know. I'm betting on it.
Yeah, so if I win, I'd like some kind of reward.
Oh, you know what I mean.
Oh, that's nice.
If I win, then what do I get?
Uh, I'll think of something.
I'll think of something?Am I thinking?
Yes, I am.
I didn't know I could win.
After all the pushing and shoving...
Thank you for your time.
Thank you for watching.
The back, you know, doesn't protect you.
I know they do.
What am I supposed to do?
I've already lost.
Something, they beat us.
But we can't win.
Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
Oh, my gosh!
Okay, so next up, the series instruction middle school...
Ogura-chan is here.
Yay!
Everyday campaign.
Now, Tanaka and Ichikawa-san and I push-sumoed.
Push Sumo?
Seriously?
Have you ever push-wrestled with me?
Yes, I have. We do it a lot at school.
So, have you ever done it before recently?
I haven't done it recently,
Not recently.
I've never done push wrestling. I haven't had a push sumo match in a long time.
It's been a long time.
Gel to gel.
Ger confrontation.
Yes.
Yay!
We're ready for a push-wrestling match!
What?
Wait, that's the least we can do.
That's awesome!
That's really funny.
Oh, my God! Let me see it!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God. One time.
One time. I'm getting choked up.
Oh, my God!
Weak!
Yes, Ishikawa wins!
Too weak?
I've never done it before.
I remember now.
That's how it starts.
It was a mind game.
Psychological warfare. We won.
I won. Thank you very much.
Three, two, one.
Yes, good!
Yes!
Yes!Yay!
That's awesome!
What?
That's great!
Start!
Start! Start!
That was the best eye trek I've ever done.
Best I've ever had.
It was good. It was clear.
And I'm glad I was able to fit it in just in time.
I don't have a lot of time, but I'm Kanoko Momota from Momochiro Clover Z.
I'm Momota.
Sorry, second time.
No, no, no, duck.
What's so great? What's that much?
It's Hiroshima.
Hiroshima.
I think I've done that before.
Really?
Maybe not.
Push.
If you push and fall, you lose.If you push and fall, you lose.
You lose.
There's also pulling.
You sure?
He's cute.
Is he strong?
Yes, he's strong.
I'm a senior, but I won't give you any quarter.
Okay, okay.
I want to win.
I want to win, too.
I want to win every game.
No, no, still.
Okay.
All right.
I'll do my best.
It's the 100th pitch.
But, because I'm scared.
Oh, it's totally strong. Totally strong. Totally strong.
I can't lose.
Oh, no, no, no.
Whoa!
Wait a minute.
Eh?
Oh-ho-ho!
Whoa!
He's strong!
I won!
Strong!
I won!We won!
That's great! What do you like?
Of course. I'm ready to listen to anything.
I'd like to disclose my contact information.
Is that okay?
Of course! Every year I can't ask and end up making it public.
Sure! Are you sure?
Of course! Every year I end up not being able to ask Kanako-chan for her contact information.
Can I cry because of that?
I'm so happy! Please do.
Sorry, it's time to go.
Are you sure you want to do that?
Let's do it.
Yes!
It's gone public now.
Congratulations.
I'm Kanako Momota.
It was Kanako Momota.
Sorry, I didn't have time.
OK!
Thank you!
Well, good morning.
Finally, because I forgot to beat the last boss,
Good luck, Ali!
Okay, here we go!
Yes, Anky, yes!
Remains!
What's this?
Yay!Yikes!
Whoa!
I'm left!
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
I'll change my face!
Oh, easy!
It looks like home,
The house has changed.